You know the rules. There
is a link in the description.
Click on that.
I will then review your Instagram
and your personal brand.
Pretty much, that's what most of you
are working towards. Pick them at random.
I'll be doing some on the road next week
with Chris. Let's begin.
And again, the amount of preparation
is zero.
What I mean by that
is some people could create
and go through and be super
organized,
but I literally pick them at random. Okay,
first thing, Hoodstahg.
Subscribe to my YouTube channel.
Interesting. First things first
is an issue.
I land here.
I don't really know what it is
that you do.
So straight away, just up here,
just tell me that.
Repairing crushed damaged cars,
like a Matt Armstrong, Petrol Head,
secondhand
car dealer, just something.
Digital creator.
Bit of a missed opportunity.
Ratios here, 300 posts,
nearly 4,000 followers.
Looks like you're cooking a bit here.
Again, Hoodstahg.
Have you got a hidden identity? If so,
potentially even just the guy in the
helmet
could be here.
The easiest way I can explain this
is on social media, we like to
build a connection with people,
with personal brands, not with a brand
logo. One thing I hate
is brand logos there or on
landing pages at the top. For instance,
I like Daniel Priestley.
I follow him.
Probably don't follow Score App.
Like Alex Hormozi,
don't follow acquisition.com.
Like Chris Williamson,
don't like Athletic Green.
You know what I mean.
We build connections with people,
so even if it was just the helmet here,
I would
rather it was that. 26 weeks ago, 2025.
Brother, you don't even post. You
were doing well. What happened?
Oh, look, you're 24,000 subscribers. See,
look. Okay.
Looks like this is cooking on your
YouTube, and you posted one month,
three months,
five months.
I think we've chatted to each other
before. Okay.
Now, you're active on your Instagram.
You've got 24,000 subscribers.
That's great.
I still think we need an identity.
Hoodstahg can be a brand,
but I kind of want to know you.
And don't give up on that Instagram.
Just keep peppering stuff across.
You chuck any of these into a platform
called Opus, and if you don't know, you
basically chuck clips in here,
AI chops them all up
and can help you with your
cadence. Are they the best? Not really.
But if you look at actually,
show them how the sausage is made, James.
Show them how the sausage is made.
If you ever see this blue text, it's
gone through Opus. Charging $75.
You see how the screen has
been chopped here,
and then later on it goes full screen?
Opus does all that.
If you were to go to your local coffee
shop, you can have a chat with the owner,
or
you could just go in there,
chat to the staff.
And they are just ripped from my YouTube
videos. All right, let's have a look.
Racing random people in my Civic Type R.
Oh. Doesn't look very legal.
Sending it at 700.
So we've got some good views here from
three years ago.
I would like to see a different set.
I know Matt Armstrong and
that seem to do it.
Maybe this is just part of your brand,
covering your ears or whatever it is.
The views are pretty good.
The reason why I have to sell my cars.
I haven't uploaded in three months.
Let me explain why.
[object rolling] From outside,
it looks like nothing's been happening,
but
inside here, it's been absolute chaos.
[object clattering] Okay.
Now,
I think you messaged me about six months
ago, and I think your biggest
concern was that you weren't sure how to
monetize.
Because here's the problem, and this
is the problem why potentially you're not
posting so much anymore.
For you to live off views,
it's going to be very, very
difficult because they just don't pay
that well,
and this should be a lesson to any
brand and personal creator out there.
Petrol Head,
love making content, but 10, 20,000 views,
50,000 views,
it's just not going to be enough. Now,
what's annoying here is a guy called Matt
Armstrong who has done this incredibly
successfully.
I have the utmost respect for this guy.
You know everyone's talking about the
"Manosphere" documentary.
I haven't seen it.
I don't think I'm going to watch it.
For someone like this actually
is more of what would
epitomize masculinity. In the pandemic,
this guy's working in an Indian
restaurant serving tables.
He's in a loving relationship.
He's got a dog.
And he posts a video of repairing his
girlfriend's car, and he realizes that
gets more views than any of his BMX stuff.
Because I'm pretty sure he started this
brand as a personal brand, as a BMXer.
So if we go to his old stuff,
it's all BMX and stuff, right?
And where was the point? Here it is.
So from 2,200 views to first car video,
15,000
views.
And then he starts to see a pattern
emerge.
You see that the car videos end up being a
lot more outliers.
Fast forward a few years,
he has one of the strongest personal
brands in the world.
He's getting a million views a day on some
of his videos. Now, this is the issue.
Matt is the exception to the rule. He
is the outlier.
He is the anomaly.
And although he's done fantastic,
Matt could
live off the monetization because of his
views alone, which leads a lot of people
to think that they can live off the views,
and I just don't think that is a very
accurate way. Let's try and do it again.
I'll show you now.
If we go to my YouTube Studio,
my main channel, and lifetime.
First things first, £113,000.
Who's got that?
Clever little marketing trick my manager
does.
He goes, "Yeah, just send it to me,
then I'll send it to you." Come to think
of it,
he's got a bigger house than me. Anyway,
that can seem amazing, but when you
realize 2017, nine years,
it's less than minimum wage
just in views.
So even with a relatively large channel,
it's just
not the way you want to survive,
ladies and gentlemen.
Wish you all the best, bro.
But what happened is,
I think you optimized the channel
and a brand without a
product in mind. For any of you that
are considering it, whatever you do,
whatever
you talk about,
must work backwards from that problem
that you solve and whatever
you do. These are quite cool. These
are literally people that gave their stuff
across to be critiqued yesterday.
So do put in your email address.
Think of it this way.
I know some people are kind of scared
that I'm going to be really mean,
but I'm not
mean from a place of hatred.
I'm mean because I want you to do better.
Okay.
Retentiond. I quite like the name.
Marketing agency.
We turn your one-time buyers into repeat
customers.
I hate those emojis for a start.
Stop that.
Retentiond,
you've done really well with the handle.
I actually really like that,
and I kind of like this periodic table
design here.
But let's just have a look. Cadence. Okay,
you're getting some posts out there.
Okay. Now you're a marketing agency.
I wonder if this is a marketing agency of
one.
Again, exactly like I said before,
there is no personal brand
here. This is a company.
You're trying to run a faceless account.
Now, the difficult thing with this
is people build bonds with people.
This is the type. This looks great. Right?
[gentle music] Love the song.
Nobody wakes up thinking about your
product. They wake up thinking about...
Cool,
but this could've been made a good reel.
Videos like this just do not do well.
You got five likes.
I think that's generous. Okay.
Whoever it is running this page,
I need you to step
up and get the fuck in front of the camera
and start talking to me because I can
make these little videos.
You're trying to game it, right?
You're turning a flipping picture into a
video.
But this just isn't going to get
What you want? I don't understand.
You're trying to do it faceless. Cool.
Again, they're not the brands
that I'm going to fuck with.
Retention can be a business,
but I need you as the person at the front
and
center. Even what I'm doing right now,
I'm putting myself at the front and center
so you can talk, you can listen to me,
I can give you my opinions. Yeah.
And the way you're trying to create this,
with the little black and white thing, it
could work. I fucking highly doubt it,
though, because let's have a look.
100 views here and there. Cool.
Represent your brand.
People trust people.
This could be a fucking AI account.
This could be someone's Claude bot,
just fucking [growls] .
And for that reason, I'm out. And again,
that's not me being a dick.
That's me just saying fucking get out
here.
Okay, Sam Haston.
This picture needs a little bit of work.
Looks like an iPhone picture.
Just looks a little bit fuzzy,
and you're a bit far
away. Fat loss specialist with a flame.
Don't know if I like that emoji.
"Fat loss made simple for you.
Struggling to lose fat?
Book a consultation below." This needs a
bit of work, right?
Because unfortunately,
you look like every other fucking
boring fitness twat on the internet.
"Fat loss made simple for you.
City Fitness, Hereford Street.
Struggling to lose fat?
Book a cons..." In a world of everyone
doing the same thing, just try and be a
little bit different. If I
was to hang out with you for a few months,
you
might have a dry sense of humor,
something.
There's something called an idiosyncrasy
that makes us all unique.
Okay,
I like these images here with representing
the amount of weight that people
have lost,
but let's get into your content.
Means absolutely nothing.
All right. First video I've ever seen.
I'm going to say this nicely.
I hate you, right?
That you've come on my feed,
I'm scrolling in bed, I'm
next to my fiancée in bed.
We're talking about our three grateful
things.
We go, "Do you know what?
Shall we have a little scroll in bed
together?"
Means absolutely nothing.
Fuck off. Who are you?
You're a fucking pedo hiding in the
dark, trying to pounce out
and grab children at night.
That's what I'm thinking here.
If you've just started at the gym,
you need to get this down ASAP before you
fall
off.
Okay, quite the accent there, fucking.
You need to make a plan. First thing,
what is your-
Okay, a little bit moany
and a little bit condescending,
and that's coming
from someone that can be quite
condescending
Fuck you not being bothered
Okay, you're trying to be in your face,
trying to stop people in their
track.
I just don't think we have the authority
for this yet.
Get in the gym. You've got a goal n-
Bro,
you look like you're dressed to go out on
a night out.
So you're the personal trainer.
You're in a fucking black shirt with a
collar.
You're either going to go be a bouncer at
a club, or you're going to a fucking
mate's engagement party or something.
Just feels a little bit off.
I don't like filming in the car either
And the next day, and you're like,
"Holy fuck you not being..."
And the next day-
Hold on. Have I just missed your hook?
It's just like I walked in on a
conversation
Fucking... And the next day,
and you're like, "Holy fuck off."
[laughs]
Who are you talking to? What's that?
I hate the transition.
To lose-
You got 59 likes on that.
[upbeat music] That's a bit weird.
[upbeat music] I hate the music.
Fuck you.
You have no idea what the fuck I deal
with. Ah.
This is why your scales have gone up over
the week-
Don't like your hooks.
Don't like your demeanor, I'm afraid.
As a small account, you
are going to have to play the game a
little bit.
Soften the tone, use props, use analogies,
stop filming in your car, stop
having the camera so close to your face.
It looks like you've changed it up quite a
bit recently, but this brash,
in-your-face approach I don't think
is going to work.
You've also got to dress the right way for
your audience.
Even now,
I'm wearing a vest because I'm here.
I'm here to fuck.
So yeah, we just got to work on that.
100 posts,
so I'm not going to be too in your face
and a brash either,
but this just is average as fuck. And
booking a consultation,
nobody woke up today going, "Fuck me,
I want a
consultation." Ultimately,
I'd bin all of this. You won't regret it.
Book in a free consultation. Look at this.
"Want to finally get rid of
that belly fat?
Want to be the role model your kids should
look up to?
You've come to the right place.
Book in a free consultation to get
started.
You won't regret it." It's like some
fucking 1970s sales
spiel. Yeah, not a fan, mate,
if I'm honest. I would get rid of this.
I would start posting like your life
depended on it.
I would, as quickly as possible,
I would take your offer offline if I
were you.
I would try and get your views up to 1,000
to 2,000 a day, and then I would try to
identify an outlier with all of your
clients as to what seems to do better than
something else.
Then I would create some kind of lead
magnet.
If people are obsessed with recipes,
make a recipe book.
If they're obsessed with glute hip
thrusts, create something for that.
But yeah. Also, if you're a PT,
it looks like you've got clients in
the gym. Why not let's get through... Oh,
you've got some of this, actually.
Here's a variation of a Bulgarian split
squat you can try if you get a sore foot
from rec-
So that little thing here could've been,
"Here's a Bulgarian split squat
variation." Okay.
Or the hook could've been better.
We could've filmed yourself stumbling,
tripping over, being imbalanced.
You could even say,
"If you don't like squats,
here's a great alternative." We
could've used something like,
"You're doing a split squat wrong." You
could've said
something like,
"Why never to put your foot on a bench for
a split squat." You
should be like,
"Never put your..." I'll do your accent as
well.
"Never put your foot on a bench for a
split squat because it's fucking unstable.
Instead,
this is what I do with my fucking client,
Sally.
What I do is I put one of these pads on
the bar, and she's so much more
comfortable. The best part is,
because we're in a squat rack,
she can put her hand
on the side for balance." Another top tip
is that people don't
realize... With your foot stance,
you could widen it a little bit, but
that was
fucking six months ago, cunt.
Six months ago.
So you need to,
there's a whole lot of work there.
But I wish you all the best.
Could've been worse.
You could've been a pussy who didn't put
their email address
in for a little bit of a roast. And yeah,
it's things, the advice,
but the amount of people that I bump into,
they go, "You roasted me,
and my life's better because of it." Did
that ever happen? It could.
There'll be links to work with me in the
description as well. Octane UK. Hate this.
Absolutely hate that. First thought,
I've got this on
a 16-inch MacBook Pro, right? 16 inch,
and I can't see what
the fuck that is. Feel the moment, resi...
I don't know what this is, right?
So I'm looking at this.
If you said,
"I'll give you a million pounds,
tell me what that is," I haven't got
a clue.
Yes, people.
[laughs]
Did not enjoy that.
[upbeat music]
So it's a club.
Pop forward. [upbeat music]
I'm still trying to figure out what it is.
So whatever this is,
let's please just tell me, are you
a DJ? Fuel the movement.
Are you a record label? Are you the club?
I don't know.
I have no bloody idea. So
if you could just establish what that is.
That's the thing I struggle with.
I come here, I don't know what you are.
But looks like you have some banger
venues.
Oh, back in the day, Ministry of Sound.
Oh, fuck.
Do you know what? Experienced success
is a wonderful thing, don't get
me wrong. But there are days that I--
Back in the day,
I could just go to Love Box
or SW4, drop a couple of fucking pills,
get in a K hole,
no one was to say anything. And now,
take a tab of LSD,
someone wants to tell me
how much they like my book.
And I'm really sorry,
but I'm tripping on LSD.
JHP Living. Right,
just going to throw this out there.
You've got the name Jamie Harrison Payne.
I guarantee that is a handle
that you could have.
JHP Living, this photo, not great. Again,
don't know what you do.
Quit the 9 to 5. Building freedom.
Life across Southeast Asia.
Stories, culture, contrast.
Don't know what you do. Full stories
and longer videos.
You want me to click this,
I don't know what you do.
3.6K subscribers, not bad.
Terrible photo as well.
They just look like crappy iPhone 11.
"A road through northern Thailand with no
real plan." Didn't do too well.
"This reset me." "Solo travel." No one
really cared.
"What it's really like."
Okay, so looks like traveling a bit,
love that.
Telling stories, making content,
People are just not resonating with this.
Now, what I would say is,
before we try and fix
this, what or how or why
is this feeding your
business? So another thing here
is you've got me to go from your
Instagram to your YouTube,
but your YouTube's taking me back to your
TikTok and
your Instagram, which makes no real sense.
So what is it you're selling?
Let's have a look at popular videos. Okay.
Your most popular video is 15,000 views,
and you've done
281 videos.
And in the nicest way possible, I would
say maybe I'm not sure what's going on
here. Let's go back. Quit the 9 to 5.
Building--
I don't know what you're working towards,
if that makes sense.
And maybe these videos would perform
better and do better if
you had something. Because again,
if you're trying to build a brand and
live off views,
that just strikes me as a very difficult
thing to do. Common theme.
Could be the thumbnail for this video.
Who knows? Right, where were we? Okay.
Casatelli Photography. Okay.
Don't mind this
photo. UK, 579, 68 posts. Cool.
Helping couples plan,
capture, and relive their day. Right.
My main concern here.
Let's have a little look.
Some of these are pretty bloody nice.
I'm just trying to find out.
Spent on 60 posts.
How long have you been posting for,
brother? 2023.
Okay, it's now 2026,
so that's three years.
68 posts, 20 posts a year. Brother, that's
not even a post a fortnight. So already,
I would say we've got a slight
issue here with cadence of how many photos
you're bloody taking.
These are quite nice. Don't get me wrong.
[humming] Again, I could be
wrong with this. [upbeat music]
But I reckon here, right,
Joey,
I would love to see someone in your
position.
Now,
I know nothing about wedding photography,
and I'm not going to take photos at
my own wedding. But if you
were to turn up and be like,
"Tell me why I need it and
what I should do, what I shouldn't do.
Show me some of the moments
that you've captured." You could be like,
you could
make a reel.
It's essential you have two photographers
on your wedding day, and
this is why. Great hook.
Suddenly I'm like,
"What?" Not every moment can be
captured by one person.
That's why we have one person
that aims at the
bride and groom and someone else
that focuses on everyone else.
I'm just making this up, by the way.
For that reason, it's essential
that you do not take anyone on board
that says to
you that one photographer is enough. Boom.
Straight away,
you've now planted Inception in my mind
like Leonardo
DiCaprio, where I'm like,
"I'm not the same." Wedding day.
Babe, who are photographers?
How many have we got?
So there's just one thing off the cuff.
Then black and white versus colored.
What's the point in that? I don't know.
Could you educate me?
Now, if you were to turn up,
and every time I watch your videos,
I'm like, "Wow,
never thought of that. Wow,
never thought of that." Whether it's a
table
arrangement at a wedding,
whether it's the time of day,
whether it's you planning
the sunset,
whether it's the weather forecast,
whatever it is,
portraits, whether
or not to have video at a wedding,
I could go on and I know
nothing about your niche.
I've taught myself more talking out loud
than your page
has done in fucking three years.
Do you see the problem?
Because if I was to see some videos from
you telling me this shit, I'd go, "Do you
know what? I'm giving this guy a follow,
and when I get fucking married, he's the
one I'm messaging. And even
if he's five grand more than everyone
else, I'm hiring
him because he knows what the fuck he's on
about." But unfortunately, when I look
at your stuff here, I'm like,
you're showing me a couple pictures of
other people's
weddings. Cool. I'm hardly frothing going,
"Fuck me, I need this
guy." And this is probably the same to any
photographer because all of you make the
same mistake of just posting fucking
pictures of other people's shit,
and we go,
"We don't care." We don't care.
The only thing I've got in mind
is my own wedding
that I've not even got a date for yet,
and I've certainly not got a photographer
yet. And actually,
here's the fucking point.
I will pay good money for someone to take
pictures of my wedding.
I've got no one in mind,
and not you either,
because you've not done
anything yet to convince me
that you're the man for the job.
So if you want the fucking job,
you've got over a year, maybe two, and
fucking convince me.
And I think it'll be a real shame.
Now I've looked at your profile,
algorithmically,
I should be getting your feed
when you start turning the fuck up.
Because again,
why should I pay you to turn up for my
wedding when you don't even
turn up for your own fucking brand?
That's a telling off because you've got
potential, mate, I reckon, even though
you're from Essex. So yeah.
How about you fucking-- I couldn't
name you one wedding photographer.
When people mention a name.
Who rebuilds crashed damage cars?
Matt Armstrong.
Handsome personal trainers, James Smith.
Lads that sell PDFs, Sean Casey. Turkish,
Durag Cartel.
Edits her photos, Courtney Black.
Whatever it is. All right.
Ryan Walker Content.
You got a blue tick, 600 followers.
Bit sus. All right?
Usually, if you're going to buy one,
do it at 10K. All right.
More content won't fix a weak message.
Strategy-led video marketing for
businesses.
What do you know about more content?
You've done 34 posts, brother. 34 posts.
I get everyone can be new, but still.
Work with me.
So these clients you work with, where
are they?
Let's get into some of this, all right?
Because I agree with the views thing
It's like there's no hooks here.
That's why I don't like these little, "Oh,
this
week I'm going to post three videos." I
get to trying to
be contrarian, but look,
going to throw it out there,
if you're going to have
content in your name,
you need some level of authority in this.
And although more views alone don't help,
that's what most
businesses want is some level of exposure,
some level of interest,
and I think you're going to have to
demonstrate your skills here,
and I don't think
you're doing it yet. 34 posts just isn't
enough.
You're just saying the same thing over
again. Talk to me about some strategies.
Get a whiteboard out.
Teach me some analogies.
Because you're saying here it won't fix a
broken strategy. What is your strategy?
Because it looks to me like your strategy
is to get discovered on Instagram, that
you're not doing that well,
to get people to click on your link to
book to work
with you. Your sales funnel
is social media, views, interest,
book a call.
But then you're saying more views don't
equal more sales.
But how are you getting sales in the first
place?
Yeah, there's quite a lot here to unpack,
if I'm completely honest.
No offense,
if you're not big in the content scene,
you're going to have to
convince me you know what you're on about,
and I just don't think you've done that
for me enough in that.
So next time I see a page,
I want there to be hundreds.
Hundreds more posts. Okay,
Josh Anders here.
Hate this logo. Sorry, just hate it.
Not connecting with it.
But let's have a look. Ooh, 2,500 posts,
7,000 followers.
That's quite a lot of posts,
but let's have a look. Joinery.
Laser cutting.
Cutting splines and pine boards.
4,000 likes though.
Can you do me a favor?
When you're editing these,
can you just tell me what you're
doing? Because this
is all good here in the ASMR,
but I'd just love to hear you
being like,
"Today we're just taking the edges off
this wood because it's about to
fit in a cabinet.
We're building this cabinet for a customer
of ours." Turn
each one into a little story.
I want to know what's happening. Now,
your content's getting shown to quite a
lot
of people, I assume. Yeah,
people love this shit.
Look, 36,000, 9,000, 12,000. This
is incredible. 16,000.
There are so many woodworkers,
DIY dudes out there watching this.
Just please,
can you tell me what you're doing?
Because I'd love to know more.
I genuinely would.
I would love to know more.
And I'm going to show you exactly who
is the fucking
daddy in this.
I had to convince myself to go to sleep
the other night because I
was in a fucking vortex watching this
guy's stuff. Look at the views on this.
Look at the views, brother.
Let's watch one together, shall we?
You understand we're watching a story
right now.
We're watching a story unfold,
and it's just a geezer at work.
He's just a guy at work, doing his job,
yet it's a beautiful thing
watching a story like this. 54,000 likes.
I get that for this lad,
he could just do the job and get paid or
whatever,
but he's just decided to record a little
bit of what he's doing and
talk over the top with it,
and it means that we can come along for
the journey.
Do you understand how many people
are out there?
I met a guy on Saturday night who has a
construction business and doesn't have
Instagram, doesn't have social media.
I go,
"So all these beautiful transformations
that other people are paying for,
you don't put on social media,
right?" This video that's getting him
54,000 fucking likes.
Someone else is paying him to do this.
You understand that, right?
So them bricks, them staff, that concrete,
that pool,
that garden, that house, that mortgage
is being paid for by someone else.
Someone else has paid for his whole
fucking film set, and he's using his
iPhone that's probably fucking through the
business to record it.
Someone else is paying for everything,
and do you know what he's going to get
from
this? Inquiries.
So many fucking inquiries.
Let's carry on.
It's just beautiful to watch.
Now let's have a look at a minger one
because I
remember last night I
was watching one with Tay in
bed. It must've been on TikTok.
The minging ones are the best ones. Yes.
Each one of these, what a story.
All right, 26 mil.
For so many of you,
what you do for work is a potential story.
Look, gym off limits, entertainment,
business media, pool guy,
shop. He kept merch. He gets some pool...
And do you know what?
People are going to buy this just because
they like him.
Just because they like him.
You know you're out there, right?
Some father is getting a fucking pool guy
mug for Father's Day because the
missus catches him watching these all the
time. I love it.
I love to see it. All right,
so back to my point.
Any of you out there
that kind of work in these trades,
you have the ability to
tell a story. So
when you're doing the woodwork
and everything like that, people
are drawn to it. Matt Armstrong, we
were talking about earlier.
Every single one of his videos
is a little story.
"Addressing the rumors about the wrecked
Bugatti Chiron." What a fucking title.
15,000 views per hour.
"Attempting to start the wrecked Bugatti
Chiron."
"How I'm going to rebuild it." "Modifying
my wrecked Ferrari." So there's just
so many stories here,
and people love stories,
and it's just a wasted opportunity
if you don't maximize that. And this
is a reason why you don't send people to
social media versus your website,
because then you just end up scrolling
like this.
Guys, be brave.
Give me your email address.
Put yourself forward for a critique.
I'll try and be kind.
If you want to work with me,
link in the descriptions.
If you want free stuff from me,
If you've enjoyed this,
you'll love this video right here.
Bye-bye.